<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://blog.blissos.org</id>
    <title>Bliss OS Blog</title>
    <updated>2021-12-24T04:45:21.296Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://blog.blissos.org"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://blog.blissos.org/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>The Blog Site for Bliss OS - And Open-Source operating system for PC&apos;s based on Android Open Source Project</subtitle>
    <logo>https://blog.blissos.org/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://blog.blissos.org/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2021, Bliss OS Blog</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a Blissful year this was]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.blissos.org/post/what-a-blissful-year-this-was/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.blissos.org/post/what-a-blissful-year-this-was/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-12-19T09:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Non-Profit Growth</strong></p>
<p>Over the last year, there has been a lot of change within the Bliss infrastructure. Some of the changes happened with moving the non-profit we initially started (Bliss Family of ROMs) to a new name (BlissLabs), along with narrowing our mission a bit and restructuring as a meritocracy based org, much like Apache.org is structured. This allowed us to give the separate projects the freedom and resources they needed to grow and succeed further.<br>
With those changes in place, we setup each project with the ability to collect donations and sponsorships, allowing each project to have an actual funding budget for the first time.</p>
<p>The BlissLabs website has been updated to reflect many of the changes to our org so far. You can find that at: <a href="https://blisslabs.org">blisslabs.org</a></p>
<p><strong>Adding a New Project</strong></p>
<p>This year we also teamed up with Waydroid projects Lead Developer, Erfan Abdi, and helped on a few things with that project, as well as allowing it to become the first project on OpenCollective underneath the new BlissLabs fiscal host. We have also since added Bliss OS inderneath that host as well. One of the benefits to helping out and learn on a project like Waydroid, is that I learn a lot from the project and it's developer(s), and those lessons translate directly to Android-x86/Android-Generic Project, and that is the work that makes it into Bliss OS builds as well as Waydroid too.</p>
<p><strong>Waydroid</strong><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286168733.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
With Waydroid on Android 10 working well, and only a few minor standing issues left, I started learning what would be needed to allow for an old idea I had back in Android-x86 7.1 days, where we use a bare minimum Linux base, with a mainstream kernel, like Ubuntu, and have that boot to Android. Allowing the ease of Linux for drivers/maintainence and the GUI of Android for the user-facing side. I can picture the automotove industry finding good use of this.<br>
With that idea layed out, we started to work on defining how we would do it, and we have a couple good starts towards some solutions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Ubuntu/Waydroid hybrid builds - A traditional Ubuntu Unity based initial UI, paired with Waydroid installed by default. Allowing the user to use Waydroid within Unity, or selecting one of a few other Waydroid only sessions (using mutter, weston, etc.) for a central focus on the Android experience.<br>
Those are available on our <a href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/blissos-dev/files/waydroid/linux/alpha/">blissos-dev</a> Sourceforge.</li>
</ul>
<p>Pay attention to the readme within each releases folder. It has the info needed to login and use the builds.</p>
<p>Gallery:<br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640287907293.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<ul>
<li>A lightweight Debian integration that boots to terminal after installed, and has command line shortcuts and scripts that allow to sign on, start a linux/waydroid session, etc.<br>
Those are available on @PieroProietti's <a href="https://sourceforge.net/projects/penguins-eggs/files/iso/debian/">Penguins-Eggs</a> Sourceforge here:</li>
</ul>
<p>The bookworm and bullseye folders each have a &quot;waydroid&quot; build. Pay attention to the readme within each releases folder. It has the info needed to login and use the builds.</p>
<p>Gallery:<br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640287928389.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>We are also working on growing the Waydroid team, and bringing it up to Android 11+, but that is an ongoing process and the Android 10 version still has new pull-requests and issues filed weekly. So still very much &quot;in development&quot;. Great project though. Check out <a href="https://waydro.id">waydro.id</a> to learn more.</p>
<p>Gallery:<br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286048088.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286105686.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286117997.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286129923.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286144207.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>Bliss OS</strong><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286183418.jpeg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
We have had success using Bliss OS as the testbed for Android-x86 commits this past year with Android 11. Many of those commits are on their way upstream to Android-x86 project. And we have also gotten a good start on an Android 12 version too, using many of the changes from Android-x86 team, plus a few of our own.</p>
<p>For the Android 9 builds, our own @hmtheboy154 has taken on updating Bliss OS 11.x, and including many of the advancements made over the past year.</p>
<p>Gallery (Android 12):<br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286198160.jpeg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://blog.blissos.org/post-images/1640286205864.jpeg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>Check out <a href="https://blissos.org">blissos.org</a> to learn more.</p>
<p><strong>Android-Generic Project</strong></p>
<p>This year on AG, we also saw that project start to take shape a bit more. Some of the methods used in Waydroid and other projects directly translated to allowing AG to release it's &quot;unified&quot; tree, where we include the base changes and options needed to compile Android 10, 11, &amp; 12 builds from the same branch. This saves me a ton of work there as I can now focus on expanding the options and fuctionality of that system and allow others to use it easier.<br>
We also started promoting the efforts of the community projects that use AG this year with <a href="https://forum.xda-developers.com/t/beta-11-projectsakura-x86-for-pcs-unofficial.4329533/">Project Sakura</a> and we also added a Community Flavors section to the website.<br>
Check out <a href="https://android-generic.github.io">android-generic project</a> to learn more.</p>
<p><strong>Boringdroid</strong></p>
<p>With Waydroid coming onto the scene this year, we got the opportunity to include some of the basic features from Boringdroid into its Android 10 and Android 11 variants. This is a huge success for Boringdroid and shows that there is a good market for including into builds as a Desktop UI solution.</p>
<p>We are looking forward to what this next year brings, watching all the ideas Boringdroid Lead Developer @utzcoz brings to the table, things are going to be exciting!<br>
Check out <a href="https://boringdroid.github.io">Boringdroid project</a> to learn more.</p>
<p><strong>To Sum It Up</strong></p>
<p>We are looking forward to the new year ahead and have a lot in store for the open-source Android on PC community. Thank you all for helping share our work and keep being an awesome group of users &amp; developers.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliss & Astian, working together in the name of FOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-and-astian-working-together-in-the-name-of-foss/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-and-astian-working-together-in-the-name-of-foss/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-08-07T03:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A while back, we partnered up with Astian, the creators of Midori Browser, and have been working with their org to create a joint vision of what FOSS should look like for the Android community.</p>
<p>Through this, the next addition to our alliance with Astian has started to take form, and we are announcing the rollout of Astian Cloud, with 100GB free storage space with your trial, and soon, Bliss OS users will get 150GB of storage to help promote the new service.</p>
<p>Astian Cloud and others will soon be rolled out into updates for Bliss OS 11.x &amp; Bliss OS 14.x FOSS editions, but for those that don't want to wait, you can find Astian Suite so far on Google Play: [https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?id=7530231193074438608] (Astian Albums, Astian Camera, Astian Calendar, Astian Cloud, Astian Contacts, Astian Spika &amp; Astian VPN)</p>
<p>The apps are also in the process of being submitted to the mainline FDroid repo as well, so our FOSS builds will soon see some of that love in upcoming releases.</p>
<p>Check out the full announcement on the Astian blog: [https://astian.org/en/blog/2021/08/05/astian-cloud-blissos-love/].</p>
<p>For the Development community, we would like to announce our plan to create a vendor method for Astian as well so the entire suite can be easily included into AOSP based projects.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliss OS 14.3 - FOSS builds - 07.24.21]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-os-143-foss-builds-072421/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-os-143-foss-builds-072421/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-07-22T07:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="bliss-os-143-foss-builds">Bliss OS 14.3 - FOSS Builds</h1>
<p>A somewhat large update this round for 32bit &amp; 64bit PC's. We have also gone live with our website redesign too</p>
<p><strong>Updates Overview:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>kernel-5.10.50</li>
<li>Updated Mesa 21.1.3</li>
<li>Updates for Intel graphics</li>
<li>Updates for MicroG</li>
<li>Fixes for root (magisk) on 32bit builds</li>
<li>Lots more, check the changelog</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="builds-being-uploaded">Builds being uploaded:</h2>
<ul>
<li>BlissOS-14.3-x86-202107202034_k-android12-5.10.50-ax86_m-21.1.3_r-x86_foss_cros-hd.iso</li>
<li>BlissOS-14.3-x86_64-202107242243_k-android12-5.10.50-ax86_m-21.1.3_r-x86_foss_cros-hd.iso</li>
</ul>
<p>Known new issues:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sleep states aren't working right on a few machines. Some can cause SystemUI to restart.</li>
<li>Some machines still have volume/sound issues, use 3rd party EQ or volume control.</li>
<li>Still trying to get Bluetooth working on many devices.</li>
<li>Magisk is only for root (modules, updates, etc. are not going to work and may break things)</li>
<li>ARM/ARM64 emulation not working on some AMD CPU's</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="download">Download:</h2>
<p>Website has been updated with most recent build links.<br>
https://blissos.org</p>
<h2 id="changelog">Changelog:</h2>
<p>Check the downloads folder for the build changelog.</p>
<p><strong>!!WARNING!!</strong> The builds that use Kernel-5.2+ are no longer compatible with the AUTO_LOAD=old kernel command line option. If you are using this option to boot, then you will not be able to. It will bootloop.</p>
<p>PLEASE NOTE I recommend everyone testing to also use this in Vulkan mode or boot using gbm_gralloc (which is now the default). Vulkan mode can be done from the Advanced grub menu if you installed using the bootable installer, or if you used a different grub, you will want to add &quot;VULKAN=1&quot; to the grub entry before the word &quot;quiet&quot;. If your device doesn't support Vulkan, you can add &quot;GRALLOC=gbm&quot; to the same place in your grub entry. Sleep states should work fine after that.<br>
Other bootloop issues can also be solved by booting with GRALLOC=gbm command -line option.</p>
<p>Thanks again 😉</p>
<p>Head on over to http://blisslabs.org for info on BlissLabs or http://blissos.org for more info on Bliss OS.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliss OS 14.3 - 06.26.21 Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-os-143-062621-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-os-143-062621-updates/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-06-24T06:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="bliss-os-143-generic-build">Bliss OS 14.3 - Generic Build</h1>
<p>Since the last update, we have confirmed ARM64 emulation through ChromeOS v91's Houdini, and we have also fixed a number of DRM and Widevine problems, so apps that use those are also working now.<br>
I also spent a good amount of time updating the new documentation site: https://docs.blissos.org and adding some troubleshooting tips and guides.<br>
The build I am uploading today will not include Gearlock (no real reason, just didn't select it to include) so I will likely make another update with this combo kernel/mesa including Gearlock later in the week.</p>
<p><strong>Updates Overview:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>kernel-5.10.46</li>
<li>Updated Mesa 21.1.3</li>
<li>Updates for Intel graphics</li>
<li>Lots more, check the changelog</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>!!WARNING!!</strong> The builds that use Kernel-5.2+ are no longer compatible with the AUTO_LOAD=old kernel command line option. If you are using this option to boot, then you will not be able to. It will bootloop.</p>
<p>PLEASE NOTE I recommend everyone testing to also use this in Vulkan mode or boot using gbm_gralloc (which is now the default). Vulkan mode can be done from the Advanced grub menu if you installed using the bootable installer, or if you used a different grub, you will want to add &quot;VULKAN=1&quot; to the grub entry before the word &quot;quiet&quot;. If your device doesn't support Vulkan, you can add &quot;GRALLOC=gbm&quot; to the same place in your grub entry. Sleep states should work fine after that.<br>
Other bootloop issues can also be solved by booting with GRALLOC=gbm command -line option.</p>
<h2 id="builds-being-uploaded">Builds being uploaded:</h2>
<ul>
<li>BlissOS-14.3-x86_64-202106261907_k-android12-5.10.46-ax86_m-21.1.3_r-x86_emugapps_cros-hd.iso <strong>ARM/ARM64 working</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Known new issues:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sleep states aren't working right on a few machines. Some can cause SystemUI to restart.</li>
<li>Some machines still have volume/sound issues, use 3rd party EQ or volume control.</li>
<li>Still trying to get Bluetooth working on many devices. .</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="download">Download:</h2>
<p>Website has been updated with most recent build links. Including a couple AOSP 11 builds (Stock &amp; FOSS)<br>
https://blissos.org</p>
<h2 id="changelog">Changelog:</h2>
<p>Check the downloads folder for the build changelog.</p>
<p>Thanks again 😉</p>
<p>Head on over to http://blisslabs.org for info on BlissLabs or http://blissos.org for more info on Bliss OS.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliss OS 14.3 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-os-143-release/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.blissos.org/post/bliss-os-143-release/">
        </link>
        <updated>2021-06-18T01:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="bliss-os-143-generic-and-32bit-builds">Bliss OS 14.3 - Generic, and 32bit Builds</h1>
<p>We have a number of things to go through here, so let's not waste any time. I have decided it's time to start releasing some of the builds on a regular basis again. Starting off, we have an x86_64 build of Bliss OS 14.3 with Gapps included and arm64 native-bridge, and reintroducing 32bit (x86) builds into the mix. We also have a barebones stock AG-11 (Android-x86 11), with Boringdroid added instead of Taskbar for main Desktop UI</p>
<p><strong>New Documentation Site:</strong><br>
We had to take down our wiki due to issues beyond our control, so things are now moved to https://docs.blissos.org</p>
<p><strong>New Build Instructions:</strong><br>
We now have a couple options for compiling. You can use the instructions found on our <a href="https://docs.blissos.org/build-bliss-os/build-bliss-os-14.x">docs site</a><br>
Or you can now use the menu-driven <a href="https://github.com/android-generic/vendor_ag/blob/master/README.md">Android-Generic Project 2.0</a></p>
<p><strong>Updates Overview:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>kernel-5.10.x &amp; kernel-5.4.x versions</li>
<li>Added/Updated Gearlock</li>
<li>Fixes to bootable USB installer for Android 11</li>
<li>KVM support added to 5.10.xx kernels</li>
<li>Lots more, check the changelog</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Gearlock kernel command Notes:</strong><br>
NOGFX=0 - Do not override kernel CLI options (needed if you plan on using Vulkan mode)<br>
NORECOVERY=0 - Do not enter recovery or show countdown for it (should not combine any other Gearlock options with this)<br>
NOSC=0 - Do not supercharge the system partition/image on boot<br>
ALWAYSRECOVERY=0 - Always boot into recovery first.</p>
<p><strong>!!WARNING!!</strong> The builds that use Kernel-5.2+ are no longer compatible with the AUTO_LOAD=old kernel command line option. If you are using this option to boot, then you will not be able to. It will bootloop.</p>
<p>PLEASE NOTE I recommend everyone testing to also use this in Vulkan mode or boot using gbm_gralloc (which is now the default). Vulkan mode can be done from the Advanced grub menu if you installed using the bootable installer, or if you used a different grub, you will want to add &quot;VULKAN=1&quot; to the grub entry before the word &quot;quiet&quot;. If your device doesn't support Vulkan, you can add &quot;GRALLOC=gbm&quot; to the same place in your grub entry. Sleep states should work fine after that.<br>
Other bootloop issues can also be solved by booting with GRALLOC=gbm command -line option.</p>
<h2 id="builds-being-uploaded">Builds being uploaded:</h2>
<ul>
<li>BlissOS-14.3-x86_64-202106171155_k-google-5.10.32-lts-pledge-xanmod_m-r_emugapps_cros-hd.iso <strong>ARM64 not working</strong></li>
<li>BlissOS-14.3-x86-202106172025_k-google-5.4.112-lts-ax86_m-r_foss_cros-hd.iso</li>
<li>BlissOS-14.3-x86_64-202106181339_k-google-5.4.112-lts-ax86_m-r_emugapps_cros-hd_gearlock.iso</li>
<li>AG-11--x86_64-202106131243_k-kernel-5.4_m-x86.iso</li>
</ul>
<p>Known new issues:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sleep states aren't working right on a few machines. Some can cause SystemUI to restart.</li>
<li>Some machines still have volume/sound issues, use 3rd party EQ or volume control.</li>
<li>Native-Bridge for ARM64 is not working in BlissOS-14.3-x86_64-202106171155 build. The BlissOS-14.3-x86_64-202106181339 build has this fixed.</li>
<li>Bluetooth is not working for many devices.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="download">Download:</h2>
<p>Website has been updated with most recent build links. Including a couple AOSP 11 builds (Stock &amp; FOSS)<br>
https://blissos.org</p>
<h2 id="changelog">Changelog:</h2>
<p><strong>2021-06-17</strong><br>
  bootable/newinstaller 948027a  Apply GearLock patches #1 for bootable/newinstaller/install/grub2/efi/boot/android.cfg  [AXON]<br>
09921b6  Apply GearLock patches #1 for bootable/newinstaller/install/scripts/1-install  [AXON]<br>
80e9323  Apply GearLock patches #1 for bootable/newinstaller/initrd/init  [AXON]<br>
2cc9399  Apply GearLock patches #1 for bootable/newinstaller/Android.mk  [AXON]<br>
56a2e92  Apply GearLock 7.2.38 initrd hook  [AXON] <br>
  device/generic/common 2b00b92  Apply GearLock patches #1 for device/generic/common/device.mk  [AXON]<br>
bdd6020  Add Boringdroid  [AGP-BOT] <br>
  hardware/interfaces 52c7d4b  wifi: optionally reset the interface after setMacAddress  [Tim Zimmermann]<br>
a90abad  Generate unique random mac address per AP interface  [Veerendranath Jakkam]<br>
46fd3b5  Revert &quot;Fix so that dual access points (AP) works.&quot;  [Purushottam Kushwaha]<br>
281306e  Revert &quot;fpc: keep fpc in system-background&quot;  [Jake Weinstein]<br>
9f49e62  bluetooth: do not fatally error on unknown packet types  [Billy Laws]<br>
7856819  Revert &quot;Make sure passthrough fails initialization if required interfaces can not be initialized.&quot;  [LuK1337] <br>
<strong>2021-06-11</strong><br>
  bootable/newinstaller ff854af  Add AG build options  [Jon West]<br>
42bd3c1  Add sha sum generation  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-06-08</strong><br>
  packages/apps/Launcher3 0b3949e  Add PACKAGE_USAGE_STATS permissions  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-06-02</strong><br>
  vendor/foss d665060  Update scripts for permission generation  [Jon West]<br>
8bfe778  Revert &quot;vendor/foss: Include permissions required for Android devices. (priv-app)&quot;  [Jackeagle]<br>
cae8cc1  foss: Re-enable alarmio app  [Jackeagle]<br>
e3f3d9e  vendor/foss: Include permissions required for Android devices. (priv-app)  [Jackeagle] <br>
<strong>2021-05-31</strong><br>
  bootable/newinstaller 03dffdd  Allow us to use 32bit rusty-magisk  [Jon West] <br>
  device/generic/common f1ecaaa  Allow us to use a separate virtualbox kernel.mk  [Jon West] <br>
  vendor/foss e820929  Add x86 (32bit) support  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-05-29</strong><br>
  device/generic/common f5edf69  Bring in gpu_access from Cuttlefish  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-05-28</strong><br>
  device/generic/common 296bb90  Update sepolicy for widevine and drm  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-05-27</strong><br>
  device/generic/common 396f73e  Remove pre-1.3 drm hals  [Robert Shih]<br>
a9ab73a  Move to clearkey drm 1.3 for cros widevine  [Jon West]<br>
3b1392b  Add houdini switch  [Jon West]<br>
4e3fe32  Add switches for using Houdini or libndk NB  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-05-26</strong><br>
  manifest 12dadf5  Track our own platform_testing &amp; device/lineage/sepolicy  [Jon West] <br>
  platform_testing fa285af  Remove BluetoothInstrumentationTests  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-05-25</strong><br>
  external/llvm-   * 3ec3c51  DO NOT MERGE: android: translate soong build rules for libLLVM12  [Mauro Rossi]<br>
2438d13  android: fix build errors in Android S  [Michael Goffioul]<br>
f6d76fb  android: VNDK support for libLLVM and llvm-amdgpu-headers  [Mauro Rossi] <br>
<strong>2021-05-23</strong><br>
  bootable/recovery c600266  Revert &quot;recovery: Allow custom bootloader msg offset in block misc&quot;  [Alessandro Astone]<br>
459c667  Revert &quot;recovery: wipe bootloader message from index 0 when using custom offsets&quot;  [Alessandro Astone] <br>
  device/lineage/sepolicy 2879ae4  adapt to GSI  [Victor Bo] <br>
  hardware/lineage/interfaces 65352a0  Remove cryptfshw for PC builds  [Jon West] <br>
  manifest 4761a7f  Track our own recovery  [Jon West]<br>
54c7779  Combine manifests for PC builds  [Jon West]<br>
3820759  Prep for PC builds  [Jon West] <br>
<strong>2021-05-22</strong><br>
  bootable/newinstaller 3afc11e  Remove ext4 install option  [Jon West] <br>
  device/generic/common bc286b0  Switch to gbm as default gralloc  [Jon West] <br>
  packages/apps/Dialer 4f5db85  Improve contatcts layout  [DennySPB]<br>
f405a76  Add ability to set full screen photos for calls  [Alexey Derendyaev]<br>
393ea0a  CallRecordingAutoMigrator: Handle all exceptions  [Pranav Vashi]<br>
252fbbd  Dialer: Make recording names sortable  [Pranav Vashi]<br>
14c6feb  Add autorecord feature  [DennySPB]<br>
f5b0058  Dialer: Enable call recording for all  [Pranav Vashi] <br>
  packages/apps/Settings b2bae91  Fix formatting in Android.bp  [Jon West] <br>
  vendor/bliss b58ba73  Log private app permissions  [Jon West] <br>
  vendor/overlays e573fac  Merge changes from topic &quot;gesture-navbar&quot; into r  [Jack] <br>
<strong>2021-05-21</strong><br>
  bootable/newinstaller 9612459  Inherit initrd &amp; install tools from openthos  [Jon West]<br>
1b71379  Update Bliss OS version in filename  [Jon West]<br>
e9c4e88  Fix errors in init  [Jon West]<br>
bff7c26  Fix ext3 installation  [Jon West] <br>
  device/generic/common d76df72  Update with more permissions  [Jon West] <br>
  frameworks/base a4b91cf  Add Sleep button to Global Power Options  [Jon West] <br>
  vendor/overlays 2fd06e7  Add Gesture bar radius [3/3]  [pavanpaps]<br>
6bc63e9  bliss:[SQUASH]allow customizing the length of gesture navbar &amp; hide gesture navbar  [Anay Wadhera] <br>
<strong>2021-05-20</strong><br>
  vendor/overlays c06a7cf  overlays: Switch to ThemePicker  [Jackeagle] <br>
<strong>2021-05-19</strong></p>
<p>Thanks again 😉</p>
<p>Head on over to http://blisslabs.org for info on BlissLabs or http://blissos.org for more info on Bliss OS.</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>